funphotobox.com 2010-11-22

# FunPhotoBox - Best Photo Effects and Gif Animations. Photo Fun Online. Create funny pictures.

FunPhotoBox.com ("us", "we", "our") has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following outlines our information gathering and dissemination practices for this site (the "Site"): 

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

When you use or register for our Site we may request information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. This information includes your name, address, phone number, e-mail address, credit card number or other payment information (the “Personal Information”). Personal Information is also collected by us at other times when we specifically request it from you. We may use your Personal Information to send you information by e-mail about the services and information that we offer on our Site. You may opt-out of receiving future e-mail communications when you register for our Site or by sending a request to that effect via email to our Privacy officer. 

### Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information that a website creates for record-keeping purposes which are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies can make your experience on the Internet more useful by storing information about your preferences and choices on our Site. This enables us to customize delivery of information and advertisements. If you choose not to allow cookies, you can usually change your browser to prevent cookies. You should note, however, that disabling cookies may limit your ability to access all of the services otherwise made available on our Site. 

### Information Collected on Third Party Sites

Our Site periodically contains links to sites which have been independently developed by third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the information, materials and other content forming part of such third party sites. This Privacy Policy extends only to data collected on our Site. 

### Third-party Advertisers

FunPhotoBox allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the FunPhotoBox Sites. Currently, FunPhotobox has relationship with Google as the third-party ad server.  
Google uses cookies to serve the most relevant ads on our website. For example if you visit automobile websites, ads on FunPhotoBox.com may be related to cars. Also Google may place the DoubleClick DART cookie in your browser to understand the types of pages you visited or content you viewed. Based on collected information, Google associates your browser with relevant interest categories and use this information to show interest-based ads. Users may stand back of the use of the DoubleClick DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.   
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks:   
Google, Inc. (<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>).   
The FunPhotobox privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.   
FunPhotobox does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. 

### Security

We have reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and interception by third parties of the information under our control. However, complete confidentiality and security is not yet possible over the Internet. We assume no liability for any damages you may suffer as a result of interception, alteration or misuse of information (including your Personal Information) transmitted over the Internet. 

### Your Responsibilities

We cannot ensure your privacy if you do not do so yourself. Do not divulge your account number or password to any third party. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your account number and password. You are responsible for all uses of your account, whether or not actually or expressly authorized by you. We cannot be held responsible for any activity in your account which results from your failure to keep your own password secure. 

### Situations in Which Personal Information may be Disclosed

We may disclose your Personal Information if we are required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate to (a) conform to or comply with any law, regulation or court order; (b) protect and defend our rights or property or that of our suppliers and licensors, whether or not required to do so by law; or (c) protect the personal safety of users of our Site or the public. We also reserve the right to disclose Personal Information to appropriate authorities at our discretion when it appears that activities which are illegal. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post changes to this Privacy Policy here so we suggest you check back periodically. 

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with us, you can contact is sending email to: [support@funphotobox.com](mailto:support@funphotobox.com).
